#### jacopo.bob.calvi@gmail.com ☒







07594769585 🕓

### **ABOUT ME**

Jacopo Calvi

Transitioning from working in the coffee industry to software development, I am currently pursuing a Computer Science degree with integrated masters at the University of Sussex. Alongside my studies, I'm gaining hands-on experience through coding events, part-time dev work, and mentoring for the university.

I enjoy tackling problems, learning new things, and I take pride in my work. So far, this made me a valued member of every team I've been a part of. I am always up for a challenge, and I'm excited to see where this new journey takes me!

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Self-employed, Brighton — Freelancer

OCT 2024 - PRESENT

- Contracted to support the development of a game using Unity, WebGL, C# & JavaScript.
- Current project involves using Python, PHP and C#.

### University of Sussex, Brighton — PAL Mentor

SEP 2024 - PRESENT

- Provide academic support and guidance to peers, within the informatics department.
- Organise and lead educational workshops, such as introduction to Python and Web Development.

### Trading Post Coffee Roasters, Brighton — Production Assistant / Roaster

OCT 2021 - DEC 2023

- Lead a small team, organising and delegating daily and weekly tasks.
- Responsible for various aspects of production across multiple sites.
- Supported company's and client's shops with equipment maintenance, technical support, and training.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### University of Sussex, Brighton — Mcomp Computer Science

SEP 2022 - PRESENT

## Macquarie University, Remote — Excel Skills for Business Specialisation

AUG 2020 - OCT 2020

#### **AWARDS**

## NWERC, Delft (Netherlands) — 64th place

Nov 2024

The Northwestern Europe Regional Contest, in which teams are tasked with solving complex programming problems within a 5 hours time limit. My team was representing the University of Sussex.

## HackSussex' Coders Cup, Brighton — 2nd place

MAY 2024

A competitive programming tournament, where contestants are required to answer Leetcode-style questions within a strict time limit. The whole event was streamed and is available <a href="here">here</a>.

# PwnEd 5, Edinburgh (Scotland) — 4th place

MAR 2024

A cybersecurity event, hosted by the University of Edinburgh. This event had teams competing in CTF challenges covering a variety of different topics. My team was representing the University of Sussex.

### HackSussex' GameJam, Brighton — 1st place

**NOV 2023** 

A 24 hours event where my team won in two categories: "most unconventional controls" and "best overall". Rick's Ranch, the game we created, is my dearest project so far and I highly encourage you to play it here.